- But it can also be infrastructure projects or various strategy documents that the city develops.
It is a large part of our work - to write these opinions on consultation and during review and participate and think and think.
And pay attention to the municipality and citizens within the municipality -
- Seeing how this building plan affects the environment and the climate goals, for example in Gothenburg.
Lindholmen is an area that has been operations and industries before.
So where it has been a gap - where there may have been parking areas or arrangements - you have managed to densify with new buildings.
We see that with several houses here.
That you have received residential buildings on parking areas.
And it is a very good way to build.
You do not use new natural land, but you use the areas already in the city.
It is also an effective way to build in existing areas.
Then there is already the infrastructure - roads, bike lanes, sidewalks, road and water, electricity and all such.
My dream and vision for the organization and the city planning group is that we will continue on that track -
- That we are involved and influence and have great credibility at the municipality.
But also be able to get even further there -